http://www.centcoastfcu.com/privacy/

Privacy Page
As a Member-owned and locally based financial institution, our pledge is to be "Community Minded" by providing support to our neighbors and our entire community.
Our dependable team continues to provide strong support during these troubling times.
If you are experiencing financial hardship as a result of the COVID-19 virus, please contact us to discuss how we can help.
For our temporary hours, please CLICK HERE
About us
Membership
Awards
Community Support
Disclosures
Careers
Products & Services
Central Coast Federal Credit Union Privacy Statement
In recognition of our members' expectation of privacy, Central CoastFederal Credit Union has adopted the following privacy statement.
Central Coast will collect only the personal information that is necessary toconduct our business. That means just what is necessary to provide competitive financial products and services - no more. Information we may gather for membership, loan applications and/or to open share accounts may include your name, address,birthdate, social security number, Careers information, and credit information. We may gather general information about site visitors' browsing activities. This enables us to track how a visitor navigates through the site and the areas in which they show interest. This is similar to a traffic report: it tracks trends and behaviors of members in general, but does not identify individuals in particular.
Central Coast FCU will protect your personal information. We will maintain security controls to ensure that member information stored on our premises and in our files and computers is protected. Where appropriate, we will use encryption to protect against unauthorized access to personal records, ensure accuracy and integrity of communications and transactions, and protect member confidentiality.
Restrictions on the Disclosure of Account Information
Central Coast Federal Credit Union will not disclose confidential memberinformation outside the credit union unless:
The member consents to the disclosure;
The information is provided to help complete a transaction that the member has authorized;
Legal or regulatory requirements oblige the credit union to supply the information;
It is supplied to a vendor working on behalf of the credit union; or
It is a credit-reporting agency.
Information we may disclose may include your name, social security number,birthdate, address, account/loan balance, account/loan status, and account/loan payment history.
Employee Access and Use of Member Information
Within Central Coast, the credit union requires that confidential information be safeguarded at all times and be used only for legitimate business purposes.
The credit union takes measures to limit employee access to confidential information on a "need-to-know" basis and makes every effort to ensure that financial information is maintained in an accurate and up-to-date manner. We educate our employees about the importance of confidentiality and customer privacy through standard operating procedures, special training programs, and Central Coast's Code of Ethics.
Member Choice
The credit union will occasionally inform members of new products and services via email, mail or telephone. If a member wishes to opt out of these offers, Central Coast will attempt to honor that request. Simply notify the credit union of your wish, and you will be excluded from future offers.
Maintaining Member Privacy in Our Business Relationships
The credit union will not sell or share member personal information with a third party for the third party's own independent use. However, Central Coast occasionally contracts with outside vendors and other business partners to perform specific services for the credit union. We require these vendors to honor and safeguard the information we provide them and to follow strict confidentiality requirements.
If you have any reason to believe that your personal information retained atCentral Coast Federal Credit Union is incorrect, please call us at (831) 393-3480 oremail us at info@centcoastfcu.com. We will investigate the problem and, if appropriate, update the credit union's records.
Community Minded, just like you!
© 2018 Central Coast Federal Credit Union. Privacy Statement |Website Disclosures Site Design by TMD
